



Work Experience

Design Specialist | Ball State Digital Corps

August 2019 - Present

Focused on front-end web design and development. Experienced at project management and making time lines, task management, managing a team of people, and team communication.

Design Apprentice Ball State Digital Corps

January 2018 - August 2019

Created and animated graphics, designed web sites and coded front-end interfaces, planned and implemented branding designs.

Assistant Manager Rue 21

October 2016 - December 2017

Managed employees tasks. Communicated plans for store organization. Assisted customers and deescalated conflicts.

Assistant Graphic Designer | H&H Signs & Awards

October 2015 - September 2016

Designed logos for private businesses, along with printing and applying various designs to clothing, yard signs, and business cards. Handled customer relations and transcribed their order.

About Me

I'm a young and experienced designer with a passion for discovery and innovation. I have been working as a designer for over four years and I have focused in web and app design for about three years. On a more personal level, I have two amazing cats that I rescued named Wasabi and Sake, and I love to volunteer at animal shelters. I enjoy spending time with friends, playing with my cats, and working on passion projects while learning new things.

Skills

Certified in:

Adobe Illustrator Adobe InDesign

Software Proficient:

Adobe Photoshop Visual Studio Code

Adobe After Effects Mamp

Adobe Lightroom HTML/CSS/SCSS

Sketch Git

Balsalmiq Sourcetree

Additional Skills:

Illustration

Collaboration

User Experience and UX testing

Project Management

Communication

Time Management

Education

Bachelor of Fine Arts | 2020 Ball State University

BFA in Visual Communications

Deans List: Spring & Fall of 2018, 2019

High School Diploma 2016 Elwood Jr./Sr. High School

National Honors Society

Technical Honors Society